Contact

kayko928@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/stephanie-iseri-4517087 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Medical/Surgical Hospitals

Certifications
CMSRN

Stephanie Iseri

Registered Nurse at Kaiser Santa Clara Hospital

San Francisco Bay Area

Summary

I have worked as a medical-surgical nurse my entire 30 year nursing career. I have been an expert witness since 2005 and am comfortable with the deposition process. One of my strengths is the ability to educate Attorneys and jurors about the medical aspects of the case.

Experience

Kaiser Permanente Staff Nurse January 2017 - Present (3 years 7 months) Santa Clara, California

Med-Surg/Hematology & Oncology

Stephanie Iseri, LNC Legal Nurse Consultant 2005 - Present (15 years)

I work part-tme as a legal nurse consultant performing reviews of medical records, writing chronologies, and offering opinions regarding the standard of care that was performed. I also work as an expert witness with my specialty being Med-Surg.

Stanford Hospital and Clinics Registered Nurse 1993 - December 2016 (23 years) Palo Alto, CA

Work on a busy medical unit specializing in end-stage liver disease, cystic fibrosis, and chronic pain. Current position is as a staff nurse IV. I have been an assistant nurse manager in the past.

Santa Clara Valley Medical Center AIDS Coordinator September 1993 - August 1995 (2 years) Followed inpatient HIV cases and served as a liason to clinic staff and house staff. Provided resources to hospitalized patients. Obtained consent from post-partum mothers to test cord blood for HIV and provided HIV education.

Sequoia Hospital Registered Nurse 1990 - 1993 (3 years)

Worked on a medical-surgical floor with a specialty in HIV/AIDS. Performed general bedside nursing, as well as relief charge nurse duties.

Education

San Jose State University
Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing · (1982 - 1990)

California State University - East Bay Legal Nurse Consultant Certificate